<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
<title>U-232</title>
<description>Installer09 is the best!</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/</link>
<item>
<title>php-irc-v2 2.1 tar gz (Apps)</title>
<description>:pirate2:  :pirate2:</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=10/php-irc-v2.2.1.tar.gz.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>torrentflux-b4rt 1 0-beta2 tar bz2 (Apps)</title>
<description>torrentflux-b4rt_1 0-beta2 tar bz2</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=9/torrentflux-b4rt_1.0-beta2.tar.bz2.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>torrentflux 2 4 tar gz (Apps)</title>
<description>torrentflux_2 4 tar gz</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=8/torrentflux_2.4.tar.gz.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>FoxIt PDF Editor 2 0 (Apps)</title>
<description>:-P:-P</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=6/FoxIt PDF Editor 2.0.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>DAEMON Tools Pro Advanced v5 2 0  0348 Including Crack [h33t][iahq76] (Apps)</title>
<description>DAEMON Tools Pro Advanced

Best product for optical media emulation. All DAEMON Tools features are now available in one solution   DAEMON Tools Pro Advanced

Key features

Functionality

Mount *.mdx, *.mds/*.mdf, *.iso, *.b5t, *.b6t, *.bwt, *.ccd, *.cdi, *.bin/*.cue, *.ape/*.cue, *.flac/*.cue, *.nrg, *.isz disc images to a virtual drive
Convert images from all supported formats to *.mdf/*.mds, *.mdx, *.iso
Make .iso, *.mds/*.mdf and *.mdx images of CD, DVD, Blu-ray discs
Make a compressed disc image or split the image to several files
Protect images with password

Advanced imaging features

Create or edit images with powerful Image Editor
Burn created images to media discs
Burn images with RMPS data
Compose your own images of selected type (CD/DVD disc) with preferred file system (ISO9660+Joliet, UDF)
Master bootable discs or images
Manage your Image Collection

Media devices virtualization

Emulate up to 32 DT and SCSI devices in all
Use 4 virtual IDE devices for advanced emulation
Mount images to physical IDE/SATA devices via advanced attaching functionality
Perform image mounting to local NTFS folders
Get detailed information about physical and virtual devices&#039; properties
Customize virtual drives: change a drive letter, DVD region, etc

Advanced user interface with powerful system integration

Customize user Interface for main application and Image Editor
Use powerful Command Line Interface for automation purposes
Enable DAEMON Tools integration to Windows shell
Use File Associations to mount images right from Windows Explorer or any other file manager
Customize Windows Explorer context menu for images and virtual devices
Get quick access to your Image Catalog via Windows Explorer
Perform basic actions via handy DAEMON Tools Gadget on Windows Desktop

MountSpace - virtual disc usage statistic on-line service

Keep track of the disc image usage statistic
Find out Top 100 most popular images
Search other discs similar to yours
Search for disc images that you are missing
Browsing for most relevant gameplay videos and much more

Supported OS:

Windows 2000 SP4 32-bit
Windows XP SP3 32-bit / SP2 64-bit
Windows Vista 32-bit / 64-bit
Windows Server 2008 32-bit / 64-bit
Windows 7 32-bit / 64-bit
Windows Server 2008 R2 64-bit

Homepage: http://www.daemon-tools.cc/eng/products/dtproAdv</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=5/DAEMON Tools Pro Advanced v5.2.0. 0348 Including Crack [h33t][iahq76].torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>ubuntu-12.10-server-i386 iso (Apps)</title>
<description>With this release, the development teams decided to dive in and focus on introducing some of the new innovations we ve been imagining for the upcoming LTS cycle, and so are very pleased to be able to announce the release of Ubuntu 12.10 for Desktop, Server, Cloud, and Core products.

Codenamed  Quantal Quetzal , 12.10 continues Ubuntu s proud tradition of integrating the latest and greatest open source technologies into a high-quality, easy-to-use Linux distribution.

Ubuntu 12.10 introduces innovations that bring together desktop and cloud-based experiences, representing the next stage in the transition to a multi-device, cloud-based world. New Previews give large, clear previews of content as it appears in the Dash search results, giving users a quick way to get more information to help find what they are looking for. The new Web Apps feature makes frequently used web applications available through the desktop. A new remote log-in option now lets Ubuntu 12.10 be used as a thin client by businesses that want to virtualise their desktop applications and deliver them
to users over the network.

Ubuntu Server 12.10 includes the Folsom release of OpenStack, alongside deployment and management tools that save devops teams time when deploying distributed applications   whether on private
clouds, public clouds, x86 or ARM servers, or on developer laptops. Cloud builders now have access to two major new components: Cinder, for block storage and Quantum, a virtual networking API. Ubuntu s
Metal-as-a-Service (MAAS) bare-metal provisioning tool has been updated and now supports Calxeda hyperscale hardware based on ARM, so users can now quickly deploy services directly to bare-metal clusters, whether they re built on legacy hardware, new Ivy Bridge-based machines or the new ARM-based hardware.

The Ubuntu desktop images have been consolidated to a single improved image with a size of 800MB. This desktop image folds in the advanced partitioning options from the alternate installer (removing the need for alternate and DVD images) and introduces support for UEFI Secure Boot technology. The Ubuntu Server image remains as a CD sized image, but installs the base system from a squashfs image for improved performance.</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=4/ubuntu-12.10-server-i386.iso.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>22 Jump Street 2014 CAM NEW AUDIO x264 AC3-MiLLENiUM (Movies/XviD)</title>
<description>22 Jump Street 2014 CAM NEW AUDIO x264 AC3-MiLLENiUM                  

General

Source...............: 720p MPG File / Audio - VOSE[THANKS]
IMDb Information.... : http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2294449/
Sample Included......: yes

NOTES: Got passed the 720p for this, rotated, fixed perspective especially in the top left after rotating, cropped the excess, resized, then went to work on it :) Got the colors better, adjusted Saturation, levels, contrast, Light rays, sharpen. Audio is much nicer.

General
Complete name                            : 22 Jump Street 2014 CAM NEW AUDIO x264 AC3-MiLLENiUM.mkv
Format                                   : Matroska
Format version                           : Version 2
File size                                : 1.18 GiB
Duration                                 : 1h 39mn
Overall bit rate mode                    : Variable
Overall bit rate                         : 1 695 Kbps
Encoded date                             : UTC 2014-06-22 23:17:12
Writing application                      : mkvmerge v7.0.0 (&#039;Where We Going&#039;) 32bit built on Jun  9 2014 15:08:34
Writing library                          : libebml v1.3.0 + libmatroska v1.4.1

Video
ID                                       : 1
Format                                   : AVC
Format/Info                              : Advanced Video Codec
Format profile                           : High@L4.1
Format settings, CABAC                   : Yes
Format settings, ReFrames                : 3 frames
Codec ID                                 : V_MPEG4/ISO/AVC
Duration                                 : 1h 39mn
Bit rate mode                            : Variable
Bit rate                                 : 1 406 Kbps
Maximum bit rate                         : 40.0 Mbps
Width                                    : 720 pixels
Height                                   : 320 pixels
Display aspect ratio                     : 2.25:1
Frame rate mode                          : Constant
Frame rate                               : 29.970 fps
Color space                              : YUV
Chroma subsampling                       : 4:2:0
Bit depth                                : 8 bits
Scan type                                : Progressive
Bits/(Pixel*Frame)                       : 0.204
Stream size                              : 1 003 MiB (83%)
Writing library                          : x264 core 142 r2431 ac76440

Audio
ID                                       : 2
Format                                   : AC-3
Format/Info                              : Audio Coding 3
Mode extension                           : CM (complete main)
Format settings, Endianness              : Big
Codec ID                                 : A_AC3
Duration                                 : 1h 39mn
Bit rate mode                            : Constant
Bit rate                                 : 256 Kbps
Channel(s)                               : 2 channels
Channel positions                        : Front: L R
Sampling rate                            : 48.0 KHz
Bit depth                                : 16 bits
Compression mode                         : Lossy
Delay relative to video                  : 1ms
Stream size                              : 183 MiB (15%)
Language                                 : English
Default                                  : Yes
Forced                                   : No

Plot

After making their way through high school (twice), big changes are in store for officers Schmidt and Jenko when they go deep undercover at a local college.</description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=2/22 Jump Street 2014 CAM NEW AUDIO x264 AC3-MiLLENiUM.torrent</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>redsn0w win 0 9 9b6 zip (Apps)</title>
<description>:-P  :-/ </description>
<link>https://u-232.servebeer.com/download.php?torrent=1/redsn0w_win_0.9.9b6.zip.torrent</link>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
